# **Erwin Susanto**

Driven by the desire to learn and experiment with new technology. Currently a back-end developer who specializes in Go. Can also use NextJS for front-end related projects. Very versatile and detail oriented. Respectable work-ethic with an open mind for constructive criticism.

Indonesian
English
Japanese

- > erwins71297@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/erwin-susanto-431670209
- https://erwinsusanto-github-io.vercel.app
- > Jakarta, Indonesia
- +6281212078822

#### **ORGANIZATION HISTORY**

2015-2017

## Bina Nusantara English Club

Branding Staff, Debate Member Photography, Illustration and Design, Managing Events, Debating, Socializing.

2015-2017

# **Binus Square Student Club**

**Branding Staff** 

Photography, Illustration and Design, Managing Events

# **WORK HISTORY**

2018-2019

# PT Erajaya Swasembada Tbk.

Software Developer Intern

Software developing, problem solving, communication, decision making. Javascript.

2019-2020

## **BPR Intidana**

**IT Staff** 

Software developing, problem solving, support, web management. PHP.

2021-2023

#### PT Erajaya Swasembada Tbk.

Software Engineer

Go, goroutines, Redis, ElasticSearch, Scalyr, Open Telemetry, Sonarqube, Message Broker(Pubsub), MySQL, PostgreSQL, AWS(Google Cloud Platform), Docker, Kubernetes

In charge of creating and maintaining ERP and Promo Microservice

#### **Professional Skills**

- Reliable Communication
- Composure under Pressure
- Detail Oriented
- Problem Solving Ability
- Good Initiative
- Quick Learner
- Positive Attitude

#### **Soft and Hard Skills**

- Experience with Javascript, Go, PHP Laravel, NextJs
- Experience with good logging and error tracking with Scalyr
- Experience Documenting with Confluence and Jira
- Experience with containerization, with Docker and Kubernetes
- Experience with Swagger for ease of QA and base checking APIs
- Experience with RPC
- Experience with Open Telemetry, New Relic, and Sonarqube for code quality.

## **Education**

2003-2009

**Melaka International School** 

2009-2012

**Darma Yudha Junior High School** 

2012-2015

Darma Yudha Senior High School

2015-2019

**Bina Nusantara University** 

GPA: 3.4